const questions = {
  history: [
    {
      question:
        "Who was the Roman govonor who convicted Jesus of treason and had crucified?",
      option: ["Pontius Pilate", "Roman Emperor Tiberius", "Barnabas"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "Excavations at Pompeii and Herculaneum was directed by? ",
      option: [
        "Napoleon Bonaparte",
        "Christopher Columbus",
        "King Charles III of Naples",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What year was the Affordable Care Act AKA Obama Care Act founded? ",
      option: [2008, 2010, 2015],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many jews were killed in World War 2?",
      option: ["Around 6 million", "Around 8 million", "Around 12.5 million"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "When was the first picture of a black hole captured in space? ",
      option: ["15 November 1997", "April 10 2019", "March 4 2000 "],
      answer: 1,
    },
  ],

  politics: [
    {
      question: "How did Abraham Lincoln die?",
      option: ["Natural causes", "Unknown causes", "Assassination"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "President Muhammadu Buhari retired as a major general of the Nigerian Army on? ",
      option: ["27 August 1985", "5 Febuary 1970", "10 October 1997"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question: "Who the first Prime Minister of the Republic of China?",
      option: ["Zhou", "Li Keqiang", "Tang Shaoyi"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The assassination of _______ started World War 1?",
      option: ["Archduke Franz Ferdinand", "Adolf Hitler", "Benjamin Franklin"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: " Martin Luther King, Jr was a ?",
      option: ["socialist", "communist", "capitalist"],
      answer: 0,
    },
  ],
  Trivia: [
    {
      question: "How many hair cuts are approved in North Korea?",
      option: [22, 35, 15],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "How many people died after opening King Tutankhamun's tomb?",
      option: [22, 35, 15],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "How many TV channels are available and approved in North Korea?",
      option: [15, 7, 3],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Worlds most expensive pineapple is worth Â£10,000 and grows in",
      option: ["Britain", "Brazil", "Hawaii"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "One day my children will not be judged by th color of their ______ but by the content of their ______?",
      option: ["personality, accounts", "Skin, brain", "clothes, person"],
      answer: 1,
    },
  ],
  TechandGeek: [
    {
      question: "Google was invented by?",
      option: [
        "Larry Page and Sergey Brin",
        "Mark Zukerberg and Steve Jobs",
        "Tim Cook and Jeff Bezos",
      ],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In the year 2018, Genesys Tech Hub gave seedfunds of ______ to startups?",
      option: ["$50, 000", "$30,000", "$20,000"],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "HP stands for?",
      option: ["Hewlett-Packard", "Horse-Power", "Health-Points"],
      answer: 0,
    },
    {
      question:
        "In 1983 the term 'virus' was first coined to describe self-replicating programs by?",
      option: ["Martinus Beijerinck", "Ivanovski", "Frederick Cohen"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Pick the odd one out?",
      option: ["Java", "Qbasic", "SmallTalk"],
      answer: 2,
    },
  ],
};

module.exports = questions;
